[NEUTRAL]😐 Specialized, very specific time.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Mr. Car has a job
[EPIC]⚡ discussed.
[EPIC]⚡ We've got a workplace room.
[EPIC]⚡ create.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Let me bring this up.
[EPIC]⚡ and they can deliver their seat.
[EPIC]⚡ Then you break it and still it.
[EPIC]⚡ It's not strictly speaking legal.
[EPIC]⚡ That's called
[EPIC]⚡ Already
[EPIC]⚡ I think I found a way home. And this last job, that's how I get there. Dreams feel real while we're in the park. It's only when we wake up that we realize something is actually strange. This is our responsibility. They're not prepared for this. Dreams collapsing.
[EPIC]⚡ You
[EPIC]⚡ mustn't be afraid to dream with a big adult.